In the most Jewish city in America, debates over anti-Semitism have exploded in the final days of the mayoral race as New Yorkers appear close to electing Zoran Mamdani, a 34-year-old Muslim who does not believe Israel should exist as a Jewish state.
Okay, first of all, this is a bazonkers headline.
Second of all, okay, do the Jewish people reading this who are not Zionists understand how the effort to continuously correlate Judaism to Zionism is done by everyone else?
There should not be a Jewish state.
There shouldn't be a white state.
There shouldn't be an Arab state.
There shouldn't be a Muslim state.
There shouldn't be none.
No states.
But this is where we are in the world.
It just so happens that the one that calls itself the Jewish state is also actively enacting a genocide and has existed as an apartheid state for the complete existence of its existence, which suggests that Jewish states are apartheid states, which suggests that Jewish people like apartheid.
Do you see which suggests that if you are against apartheid, that you are against Jewish people, which is crazy.
But you see, it's the mental gymnastics.
Like, see, it's like what's happening on my shirt.
That's what they're trying to do with this.
And that's bazonkers.
Also want to show you this.
So Hakeem Jeffries decided to finally endorse Zoran Mamdani, bind you.
They Democrats from New York.
Only for AIPAC associate Elliot Malin to say we will be withholding contributions to House Democrats until further notice.
I don't know how else to put it to y'all that the government that you think is working for you ain't.
They literally aren't because it's shut down.
But let's just take a look at Israel real quick.
Israel.
That's Israel's national minister of security, Ben Gavir, showing us that they don't allow Palestinians to sit even when they are in their cells.
That is who AIPAC is lobbying the United States government to serve.
Hakeem Jeffries is supporting your tax money being sent over there.
You know, I think we also forget the connectivity in this world.
In 1948, some very interesting things happened all at the same time.
Korea was split into North Korea and South Korea.
India was partitioned into Pakistan and India.
Apartheid was supplanted in South Africa.
And the Nakba, the catastrophe, took place in Palestine by the West.